< 55143a1 feat: Add a complete build script to automate executable creation, bundling FFmpeg and Git portable.
< 074fd7c feat: Add initial PySide6 GUI application for MKV processing with configuration management and core video processing logic.
< b8284fc feat: Add core MKV video processing logic, PySide GUI, and configuration management.
> 4d1cfa6 Implement cleanup for update_installer.bat and enhance module loading debug information
> 4138c8a Add background update download functionality with progress tracking
> 0e2ac36 Implement debug mode for GUI module loading in gui_pyside.py
